《边桥谜案》前情提要
Previously on the Bridge...
真可惜戴维・泰特被美国人收押了
他杀了一个警察的儿子
要在我们这一定得让他血债血偿
我是来找新搭档的
I'm looking for new partner.
我这个人没有搭档
I don't have partners.
只有员工
I have employees.
我有隧道
And I have a tunnel.
我是同性恋  我是这个家族的耻辱
I date women. I'm an embarrassment to the family.
滚出去
非常乐意
我得到了启示
I've had revelation.
伊娃
Eva.
我想娶她做我妻子
I want to make her my wife.
但是伊娃走了
But Eva's gone.
你去哪
科洛涅阿斯
我能带你去
克罗斯警探
Detective Cross.
我的新娘不见了
My bride is missing.
我看到了一些情况
你们找的那个女孩
我看到她在警察局
伊娃・格拉
拜托
消停会儿
她需要去医院
干掉她
你是个好孩子
拜托
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com
翻译
圈圈
胖兔纯
翻译
No.Zero
wdjmhs
校对
时间轴
黑屋之零
黑屋之点
黑屋之斯
黑屋之基
imok
后期  吉吉
总监  wdjmhs
边桥谜案
第一季   第十三集
第一季   第十三集[本季终]
你还好吧
You're okay.
你还好吗
You're okay?
能帮我把刷子拿来吗
You want to go get the brush?
好
Sure.
去吧
Go get it.
你想给他好好洗个澡吗
You want to give him a good brushing?
好啊
Sure.
他需要休息一下
He needs to cool down.
我要把他卖给一个马里昂郡的人
I'm gonna sell him to a man in Marion County.
真不知道他要这匹阉马做什么
Don't know what he wants wit this cutting horse...
你要退休了吗
Are you going to retire?
退休申请在我桌上已经放了两个月了
Papers have been on my desk for two months.
卡门说我在故意拖延
Carmen says I'm stalling.
或许是吧
Maybe I am.
我必须要知道
Well, I need to know.
退还是不退
Yes or no.
暂时不退
Not at the moment.
不退
No, I am not.
很好
Good.
为什么说很好
Why is that good?
我想调查华瑞兹那起失踪女孩的案子
I want to work the dead girls of Juarez.
是关于那个...
Is this about the uh..
斯蒂文・林德的准新娘的案子吗
supposed bride of Steven Linder?
是的
Yeah.
桑娅  那个男人
Sonya, that's a man
你最好少跟他接触
you don't want to put a whole lot of stock in.
他说带走伊娃的车是美国牌照
He said th car that picked Eva up had U.S plates.
若是美国公民与此事有关呢
What if an American is involve in this?
那我们就有责任调查
It's our responsibility to do something.
责任  或许有
Yeah, responsibility, maybe.
但没有管辖权
Jurisdiction, no.
若美国公民在墨西哥
Well, if an American commits a capital crime--
犯下可判死刑的罪  如杀人
like murder-- in Mexico,
管辖权将由两国共同商定
jurisdiction is determined by both parties.
近来学习不少啊
So you been studying up.
汉克  他们一定得管这事
They have to do something, Hank.
桑娅  看着我
Hey, Sonya... look at me.
过去的十五年里
For the past 15 years,
墨西哥警方  美国警方
the Mexican police, us,
墨西哥军队  调查局
the Mexica army, the FBI,
所有人都在调查此案
everybody has been working that case.
有过几次诉讼
There's been prosecutions.
也曾经有人被判过刑
Hell, there's been convictions.
各种各样的人都被关起来了
They got all kind of people locked up,
还是有女孩死去
and still those girls die.
这是个黑洞
It's a black hole.
我想跟马可一起调查死亡女孩的案件
I want to work the dead girls with Marco.
退休后会很无聊的
You'll be bored if you retire.
感谢你们的帮助
警察局
那些女人去停尸房收获会大一些
她们也在停尸房守夜了
我知道
十五分钟后如果她们还在  赶她们走
谢谢
都出去
Out.
饮料记我账上
Horchatas on me.
我尽量不在办公室做敏感工作
I try to not use my office for my more sensitive work.
蒙特  不知怎么说
I don't know, Monte.
你有点像是得了被害妄想症
Looks like you might be getting paranoid.
留任协议
Retainer agreements.
签署后  律师和客户的保密协议就生效了
Sign these and you'll have attorney-client privilege.
我已经有律师了
I already got an attorney.
这事上你还没有
Not for this you don't.
我的费用为公司利润的百分之十
My fee is ten percent of the company's profits.
公司
Company?
什么公司
What-what company?
米尔怀特运输服务
Millwright Transportation Services.
你是首席执行官
You're the CEO.
雷和凯撒是职员
Ray and Cesar are employees.
我的同事本杰明・德拉格会帮你们
My associate Benjamin DeLarg will help you set up
在雷伯恩国民银行开一个公司账户
a corporate account at Rayburn Nationa bank.
他还会负责搞定税务局
He'll also handle the IRS.
等等
Whoa, whoa, hey.
你们达成协议之前
Whatever deals y'all be cutting,
是不是应该通知雷雷哥一声啊
someone forgot to send a memo to old Ray Ray here.
兄弟  百分之十
Bro, ten percent?
这有点多啊
That's a little steep.
这是行业标准
It's an industry standard.
毛行业  听着  德克萨...
Industry? Look, Tex...
让他说完  雷雷
Let the man talk, Ray Ray.
谢谢  凯撒
Gracias, Cesar.
水高船涨  所以是百分之十
Point is a rising tide lifts all boats, hence the ten percent.
蒙特  我们同意
We agree, Monte.
福斯托约我吃晚饭
Fausto asked me out to dinner.
我该去吗
Should I go?
当然不能  小夏
No way, Char.
夫人  我觉得这不是好主意
I don't think that's a good idea, senora.
加尔文先生不希望有人忤逆他
Senor Galvan likes to get what he wants.
他认为你很迷人  米尔怀特夫人
He finds you captivating, Ms Millwright.
我赞同这一点
An opinion I share.
告诉他我们接受他的条款
Tell him we agre to his terms.
蒙特  感谢你所做的一切
Thank you for everything, Monte.
这是我的荣幸  米尔怀特夫人
It is my pleasure, Ms. Millwright.
小夏  我觉得这事太不靠谱了
Char, I'm feeling way out of the loop here.
没什么不靠谱的  雷
There is no loop, Ray.
你要么接受蒙特的提议  要么离开
You can agree to what Monte's offering or you can leave.
就这么简单
Simple as that.
离开
Leave?
你带我来是帮你的
You brought me here to help you.
帮我
Help me?
你跟蒂姆在我背后搞鬼
You went behind my back with Tim.
我知道  对不起
Yeah, I know. I'm sorry.
我是看到了机会...
You know I saw an opportunity and..
你去给人跪舔也是机会吗
"Muff dove" was that an opportunity, too?
是她强奸我
She raped me.
真的吗  雷
Oh, really, Ray?
对  就跟某种协议一样
Yeah, it was some kind of cartel thing, you know.
那都是我应该做的
I was only doing what I had to do.
那我现在是做我应该做的  保护自己
Well, now I' doing what I have to do: protect myself.
你要不要跟我一起
Are you with me?
好  该死的
Yeah. Shit.
抱歉  宝贝
I'm sorry, babe.
给我放尊重点
Show me some respect.
怎么了  你屁股很性感
What? You have a great ass.
我是情不自禁
I couldn't help myself.
你现在是我手下
You work for me now.
凯撒拍我的屁股吗
Does Cesar slap my ass?
没有  夫人
No, senora.
埃尔帕索警局总部
你不会放手的对不对
You're not giving up on this, huh?
我就知道你会来
I knew you'd come.
见到你也很高兴
It's good to see you too.
西莉亚来找过我
Celia came to me.
她在警局看到过伊娃・格拉
She saw Eva Guerra at the police station.
什么
What?
她被关起来了吗
She's in custody?
没有
Nope.
她现在不在那里了
She's not there anymore.
所以她...
So she..
从你们警局消失了吗
disappeared from your police station?
这个我也不清楚
I don't know that.
西莉亚看到她了
Celia saw her.
目前我就只知道这个
That's all I know right now.
你跟你们队长说过吗
Did you go to your captain with this?
我需要先跟我信任的人说
I needed to talk to someone I trust first.
桑娅
Sonya...
这种事肯定是很复杂
Something like this has many layers.
也很危险
It's dangerous.
你得小心
You need to be careful.
我知道
I know.
我们得小心
We need to be careful.
这是什么玩意  蛋糕吗
What is that shit-- cupcakes?
今天是你第一天回来
It's for your firs day back.
我跟你说过我不想大张旗鼓
I told you I didn't want a big deal out of it.
就是大事嘛
It is a big deal.
来吧  看大家假装想念你会很有意思的
Come on, it'll be fun watching people pretend they missed you.
我只想回来工作  知道吗
Look, I just want t get back to work, all right?
泰特的事我们以后再告诉地方检察官
Maybe we talk to the DA about Tate, maybe...
雪莉想让你慢慢恢复状态
Sherry wants to ease you back in.
慢慢恢复状态
Ease me back in?
什么意思  去吉瓦尼斯俱乐部开个会吗
What does that mean? A Kiwanis club meeting?
米莉・昆塔纳这周六要满一百岁了
Millie Quintana turns a hundred this Saturday.
四百个词  要感人
400 words, heartwarming.
我宁愿自戳双目也不想写那种故事
I'd rather stab a pencil in my eye than write that story.
别吃什么蛋糕了  上车  我们走
Let's skip the cupcakes. Get in, let's go.
我们去搞定那个故事吧
Let's get it over with.
活得真够久啊
Oh, my God old people.
谁会想活上一百岁啊
Who wants to be a hundred anyway?
友好一点
Be nice.
电视机开着呢
The television's on.
阿德里亚娜
Hey, Adriana.
情况不妙
That does not look good.
她可能受伤了
She could be hurt.
到处看看  看看有没有后门  窗户之类的
Go, uh... go around, see I there's a back door, window.
女士
Hey! Hey, lady.
Hey! Lady.
她死了
She's dead.
我到处看看
I'm gonna look around.
我嘞个去
Holy shit.
我去
Shit.
我们得抓紧时间
We need to hurry.
你确定你看到她了吗
Are you sure you saw her in here?
确定  是三天前
Yes, three days ago.
那为什么系统里查不到
Then why is she not in the system.
不知道  但她确实出现过
I don't know. she was in here.
这里  停
There. Stop.
是她
It's her.
你认识他吗
Do you know him?
看不出是谁
No, I can't tell.
马可
Marco.
糟了
Oh, shit.
在工作吗
对
什么案子
里维拉德尔布拉沃的枪击案
这案子我没听说过
家暴  应该是家里吵架什么的
你真敬业  马可
非常敬业
哥们  为什么不眼瞎一下
Oh, hey, mama, why don't you hook a gimp up
不小心把什么扔到我车上呢
and throw a little somethin' somethin' in the back of my car?
有什么消息
What you got?
没人愿意透漏  但这真的是一大笔钱啊
Nobody would go on the record, but it's a lot o money.
一大笔是多少
No shit, Sherlock define a lot.
我听说是三千万
About $30 million is the number I heard.
一个老人守着巨款去世啊
Ooh. So, some old bitty dies baby-sitting a cartel fortune.
第一天回来上班就遇上这种事  真不赖啊
I'd say it's a pretty decent first day back at work, wouldn't you?
不仅如此
That's not all.
还有一半是欧元
Half of it's euros.
不会吧
No shit.
是啊
Yeah.
谢谢  非常感谢
Thanks. I appreciate it.
想猜猜到底是多少吗
Want to take a guess on th final count?
五千万美金
Uh, 50 million bucks.
为了从中捞一点  警方通常会估计的少一些
Cops always estimate low in case they can pocket some.
四千万美元
$40 million.
我猜的很接近
I was close.
还有两千万欧元
And 20 million euros.
那就是大约六千五百万美元
Wow. It's-it's like $65 million U.S.
两种货币都是面值一百的和二十的
All a hundreds and twenties, both currencies.
为什么还会有欧元
What is up with the whole euro thing?
这才是奇怪之处
That's the story it's weird.
真的很奇怪
It's really weird.
但是我喜欢  奇怪是好事
But I like it. Weird is good.
这是给你的
This came for you.
谢谢
Thank you.
那是什么
What the hell is that?
钱给你了
米莉・昆塔纳是谁
"米莉・昆塔纳是谁"
"Who is Millie Quintana?"
我来开车  佩德罗
I'm driving, Pedro.
你个混蛋
随你怎么说
Whatever.
屁都不懂的白人小子
把婴儿床挪到后面的房间
我得挂了
她在哪
我不懂你说什么
警察局出现过的那个女孩
她叫伊娃
你那晚当班
是不是有个派对
没有
No.
你在说谎
马可  别趟这浑水
我已经趟了
水都快淹到我屁股了
告诉我她在哪里
她怎么了
你给我小心点
你干了什么
What did you do?
她还活着
She's alive.
你说你知道我们要去哪的
You said you knew where we were going.
我知道
I do.
我们错过高速入口了
We missed the highway.
这条路更安全  雷
It's safer this way, Ray.
我过去常开着
Shit, man. I took fast boats
载满毒品的快船进入迈阿密
loaded to the rails with coke into Miami,
却一次都没被截停过  知道为什么吗
never got stopped once. You know why?
为什么  雷
Why, Ray?
因为我他妈的不在乎别人看到
It's 'cause I didn't give a shit about not being seen.
就像电影《现代启示录》里的那一幕
It's like that scene in Apocalypse Now
鲍比逼那些小子冲浪
where Bobby makes those boys go surfing
后面还有查理朝着他们的屁股开枪
with Charlie firing on their ass.
我没看过
I've never seen it.
我的意思是  偷偷摸摸反而更惹人怀疑
The point is, all this creeping around is what draw suspicion.
我要调头
I'm turning around.
-停车  -为什么
- Stop the truck. - Why?
我要下车
I want to get off.
感觉不太对
This isn't good.
我可不停
I ain't stopping.
爷们点行吗  兄弟
Grow some huevos, bro.
该死的美国佬
这是什么地方
What is this place?
这曾经是个修道院
Used to be a monastery.
现在是受难者的庇护所
Now it's a house for the damned.
伊娃在这里吗
And Eva's here?
是的  如果我们运气好的话
If we're lucky, yes.
他本来应该杀了她
He was supposed to kill her
把她埋在沙漠里
and bury her in the desert.
我们一会再谈这个
We'll talk about it later.
晚上好
马可・鲁伊兹  警察
Marco Ruiz. Policia.
谢谢
有人问起过她吗
没有  她来的时候情况很糟
她在这里很安全
不  修女
她在这不安全
跟我来
这边
她在这里
她来之后没说过一句话
看上去像被人下了药
我们要带她走
如果你们一定要这样
是的  修女  我们必须得带走她
伊娃
Eva.
你安全了
You're safe.
跟我们走  好吗
All right? Come with us.
他是好人
He's okay.
她被带去了一个派对
She was taken to a party...
下药  强奸
drugged, raped...
天知道还干了什么
who knows what else?
有警察参与吗
Police?
有一些
Some.
我们得揭发他们
We need to fix this.
现在不行  桑娅
Yeah, well, not now, Sonya.
她留在墨西哥不安全
She-she's not safe in Mexico.
我们得把她带到美国境内
We need to get her across the border.
我有个朋友
I have this friend.
他是急救员
He's a paramedic.
他能弄到救护车
He can get access to a ambulance.
帮助她穿过边境
To get her across...
你坐在后面  在边境亮下你的警徽
You sit in the back, show your badge at the border.
好吗  你不会有任何麻烦的
All right? You should not have any problems.
好吧
All right.
我能做到
I can do that.
谢谢你
Thank you.
但你要处理好这件事
But you'll do something about this.
我会的
Yes.
我不知道还能打给谁
Didn't know who else to call.
她需要治疗
I think she need medical attention.
卡门正从医院赶回来
Yeah, well, Carmen's coming back from the hospital.
她会尽力而为
She'll do what she can do,
但我怕...她需要的不止这些
But... she might need more.
来吧  宝贝
Come on, sweetie.
我整理了下你的旧房间
I fixed up your old room.
谢谢
Thanks.
上台阶
Step up.
再上
Up.
再上一阶
Step up.
你怎么把她带过边境的
How'd you get her across the border?
用救护车
Ambulance.
马可找了人帮忙
Marco called in a favor.
还有谁知道她在这里
Who else knows that she's here?
没别人了
Nobody.
你不准备告诉我发生了什么吗
So, you want to tell me what this is about?
华瑞兹的警察把她弄成这样的
Cops in Juarez did this to her.
马可让我别管这事
Marco told me to stay out of it.
那就让他处理吧
Yeah, well, let him handle it.
以他现在的状态不行
He's in no shape to handle it.
他还处于丧子之痛中
He's grieving.
我昨天看见他把一个男人揍得半死
I watched him beat a man half to death yesterday.
跟这案子有关的人吗
Related to this case?
是的
Yes.
我比较喜欢肋眼牛排
You know, I prefer, uh...the rib eye.
肥肉比较多
It's all about the fat.
我比较喜欢T骨
I prefer T-bones.
我男朋友更好这口
My boyfriend likes them better.
你从坦帕这一路走来不容易啊
Come a long way since Tampa.
我真想说雷也一样
I wish I could say the same for Ray...
我们以前见过吗
Do I know you?
福尔姆
Froome.
阿里斯・福尔姆
Arliss Froome.
我们知道地道的事
We know about the tunnel.
也知道福斯托・加尔文的事
And we know about Senor Fausto Galvan
知道吗
You know..
我们了解的事情很多  夏洛特
we know a lot of things, Charlotte.
你到底是谁
Who are you?
现在来讲
Well, right now..
我是你唯一的朋友
I am your only friend.
调查局的
FBI?
我就知道
I knew it.
不确切
No, not exactly
不过也挺好
But you know what I like,
我喜欢你的思路
I like the way you're thinking
说明你知道会有什么后果
It means that you know what' coming
什么后果
What's coming?
目前  什么也没有
Right now, nothing.
一定要去跟福斯托共进晚餐
And make sure you go to that dinner with Fausto
这事你也知道啊
How do you know about that?
我们无所不知
We know everything.
再联系
I'll be in touch.
T骨牛排如何
T-bones?
我在路上了
又买纸尿布啊
好吧  这就去买
知道了  不喝酒
该死的
你来干嘛
What are you doing here?
你的脸色好差
You don't look s good.
我在睡觉
I was... sleeping.
很晚了
It's late.
我能进去喝一杯吗
Can I have a drink
好吧
Uh, yeah
当然
Sure
进来吧
Come in.
你今天晚上怎么这么闲
Don't you have something else to do tonight.
你把那家伙打了一顿
You beat that man up.
他是警察
He was a cop.
但我们找到伊娃了
We found Eva, right?
你是警察
You're a cop.
不能这样做
You can't do that.
怎么就不能
Oh, yes, I can
我还就干了
And I did.
事情有变化  马可
Something's changed, Marco.
很多事都变了
A lot of thing changed.
阿尔玛走了
Alma is gone
女儿们也走了
My daughters are gone.
格斯死了
Gus is dead.
-我理解你的心情  -是吗
- I know what you're thinking. - Is that so?
你想宰了戴维・泰特
You want to kill David tate
他夺走了我的一切
He took everything from me.
但他却平安无事
But he's safe.
他会坐牢
He'll go to trial.
也许会被判死刑
Maybe get the death penalty.
我不知道  也不在乎
I don't know and I don't care.
不在我的掌控之下
It's out of my hands.
我姐姐丽莎被杀后
When Lisa wa murdered..
我想要凶手偿命
I wanted the man who did it to die.
我向上苍祈祷
I prayed for it to happen.
也许汉克应该当场杀了那家伙
Well, maybe Hank should have killed him when he had the chance
他永远都不会那样做
He would never do that.
当然  他是个好人
Of course not. He's a good man.
我不会有事的  桑娅
I'll be okay, Sonya.
-好的  -好的
- Okay. - Okay.
我无能为力
There's nothing I can do.
别担心
Don't worry.
我不会干傻事的
I won't do anything stupid.
我知道
I know.
你是个好人
You're a good man.
好的
All right.
晚安
Have a good night.
?Do you know how I feel?
?How I feel about you?
?Do you know this is real?
?How I feel around you?
?When I see you look at me?
?I'm not sure of anything?
All I know is, when you smile?
I believe in everything...?
Do you know how I dream?
How I dream about you?
Do you know how I feel?
请把靴子脱了
Take your boots off please
Do you know how I feel?
How I feel about you?
Doesn't take much to tell?
That I love, oh, I...?
埃琳娜给我打电话了
丹妮拉出事了
她没下公共汽车
But you're nowhere near?
No, you're nowhere near...?
妈妈
Madre...
No, you're nowhere near?
Oh, oh, oh..?
Oh, oh, oh?
对你的丧子之痛我深表同情
喝一杯吗
谢谢
Gracias.
再来一杯吧
我不知道还能给谁打电话
这20年你没求过我
你不想欠我人情
这回是怎么回事
我现在什么都不在乎了
合情合理
你在监狱里有人吧
有
埃尔帕索那边呢
哪里都有
如果有人
单独拘禁
受到严密保护
杀你儿子的那个畜生吗
不太容易
但不是没有可能
只要你说话  我马上去办  马可
我会为你宰了他
不
No
我想亲手宰了他